Kenneth D. Swegman Jr.
Software Engineer
Pittsburgh, PA. | kenneth.swegman@gmail.com

Summary

Youthful, Passionate, and Excited Software Engineer with two prior internships in developing web apps from front to back-end, and being an Admin in Azure, while using the cloud infrastructure on other development projects. Knowledgeable of Computer Security and Networking topics. Keen on taking on new and challenging opportunities in a Systems, Development, or Security role within a motivated team.

Skills

```
Azure | Powershell | Kali Linux | Power-BI SQL | HTML | CSS | LaTex Logic Apps | Data Factories
```

Programming Languages

```
Rust (currently learning) | C (Proficient) | C++ (Proficient)

Python (currently learning) | SQL (Proficient) | RISC-V (currently learning)

C# (Past Experience) | Java (Proficient) | JavaScript (Past Experience)
```

Experience

Duquesne Light Co.

Azure Engineering Intern, May 2019 – Aug. 2019

- Developed front-end using Power-BI with back-end using Azure Infrastructure
- Set up multiple servers, databases, and vms for projects in the company.

IT Intern, May 2017- Aug. 2017

• Shadowed ReactJS Developers and .Net Framework Developers.

Education

La Roche University

Bachelor of Science in Computer Science (CS) August 2015 – December 2019 Minor: Computer Security January 2018 – December 2019